Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 5: Boxes 89-110
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 5: Boxes 89-110
- Box: 93, Folder: 26 (Box 93, Folder 26)
  - Item 9: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.9 (1958:Feb. 7). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.10 (1958:Feb. 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.11 (1958:Feb. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.12 (1958:Feb. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.13 (1958:Mar. 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.14 (1958:Mar. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.15 (1958:Mar. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.16 (1958:Mar. 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.17 (1958:Mar. 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.18 (1958:Mar. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.19 (1958:Mar. 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.20 (1958:Mar. 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.21 (1958:Mar. 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.22 (1958:Mar. 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.23 (1958:Mar. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.24 (1958:Apr. 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.25 (1958:Apr. 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.26 (1958:Apr. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.27 (1958:Apr. 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.28 (1958:Apr. 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.29 (1958:Apr. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.30 (1958:Apr. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.31 (1958:May 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.32 (1958:May 2). Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.33 (1958:June 2). Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.34 (1958:June 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.35 (1958:June 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.36 (1958:June 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.37 (1958:June 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.38 (1958:June 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.39 (1958:June 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.40 (1958:July 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.41 (1958:July 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.42 (1958:July 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.43 (1958:Aug. 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.44 (1958:Aug. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.45 (1958:Sep. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.46 (1958:Sep. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.47 (1958:Sep. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.48 (1958:Sep. 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.49 (1958:Oct. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.50 (1958:Oct. 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.51 (1958:Oct. 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.52 (1958:Oct. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.53 (1958:Oct. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.54 (1958:Nov. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.55 (1958:Nov. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.56 (1958:Nov. 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.57 (1958:Nov. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.58 (1958:Nov. 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.59 (1958:Dec. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 60: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.60 (1958:Dec. 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 61: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.61 (1958:Dec. 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 62: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.62 (1958:Dec. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.63 (1958:Dec. 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 64: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.64 (1958:Dec. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 65: Information Bulletin Index: 1958, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
  - Item 66: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.2 (1959:Jan. 7). Item is in English.
  - Item 67: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.3 (1959:Jan. 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 68: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.4 (1959:Jan. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 69: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.5 (1959:Feb. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 70: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.6 (1959:Feb. 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 71: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.7 (1959:Feb. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 72: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.8 (1959:Feb. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 73: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.9 (1959:Feb. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 74: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.10 (1959:Feb. 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 75: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.11 (1959:Mar. 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 76: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.12 (1959:Mar. 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 77: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.13 (1959:Mar. 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 78: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.14 (1959:Mar. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 79: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.15 (1959:Mar. 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 80: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.16 (1959:Apr. 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 81: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.17 (1959:Apr. 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 82: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.18 (1959:Apr. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 83: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.19 (1959:Apr. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 84: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.20 (1959:Apr. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 85: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.21 (1959:Apr. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 86: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.22 (1959:May 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 87: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.23 (1959:May 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 88: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.24 (1959:May 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 89: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.25 (1959:May 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 90: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.26 (1959:May 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 91: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.27 (1959:June 2). Item is in English.
  - Item 92: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.28 (1959:June 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 93: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.29 (1959:June 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 94: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.30 (1959:June 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 95: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.31 (1959:July 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 96: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.32 (1959:July 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 97: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.33 (1959:Aug. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 98: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.34 (1959:Aug. 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 99: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.35 (1959:Sep. 2). Item is in English.
  - Item 100: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.36 (1959:Sep. 2). Item is in English.
  - Item 101: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.37 (1959:Sep. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 102: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.38 (1959:Sep. 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 103: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.39 (1959:Sep. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 104: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.41 (1959:Nov. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 105: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.42 (1959:Nov. 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 106: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.43 (1959:Dec. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 107: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.44 (1959:Dec. 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 108: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.45 (1959:Dec. 7). Item is in English.
  - Item 109: Information Bulletin Index: 1959, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
  - Item 110: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.1 (1960). Item is in English.
  - Item 111: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.3 (1960:Feb. 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 112: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.5 (1960:Feb. 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 113: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.6 (1960:Mar. 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 114: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.8 (1960:Mar. 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 115: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.9 (1960:Mar. 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 116: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.10 (1960:Mar. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 117: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.12 (1960:Apr. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 118: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.13 (1960:Apr. 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 119: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.14 (1960:Apr. 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 120: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.15 (1960:Apr. 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 121: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.16 (1960:Apr. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 122: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.19 (1960:May 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 123: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.20 (1960:May 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 124: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.21 (1960:June 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 125: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.22 (1960:June 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 126: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.24 (1960:July 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 127: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.26 (1960:July 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 128: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.27 (1960:July 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 129: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.28 (1960:July 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 130: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.31 (1960:July 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 131: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.32 (1960:Aug. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 132: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.33 (1960:Aug. 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 133: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.34 (1960:Aug. 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 134: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.35 (1960:Aug. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 135: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.36 (1960:Aug. 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 136: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.37 (1960:Aug. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 137: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.38 (1960:Aug. 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 138: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.39 (1960:Sep. 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 139: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.41 (1960:Oct. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 140: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.42 (1960:Oct. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 141: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.43 (1960:Oct. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 142: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.44 (1960:Nov. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 143: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.45 (1960:Nov. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 144: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.46 (1960:Nov. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 145: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.47 (1960:Dec. 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 146: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.48 (1960:Dec. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 147: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.50 (1960:Dec. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 148: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.51 (1960:Dec. 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 149: Information Bulletin Index: 1960, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
- Box: 93, Folder: 27 (Box 93, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.1 (1961:Jan. 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.2 (1961:Jan. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.3 (1961:Feb. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.4 (1961:Feb. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.5 (1961:Feb. 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.6 (1961:Feb. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.8 (1961:Mar. 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.9 (1961:Mar. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.10 (1961:Mar. 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.11 (1961:Mar. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.12 (1961:Mar. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.13 (1961:Apr. 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.14 (1961:Apr. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.15 (1961:Apr. 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.16 (1961:Apr. 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.17 (1961:Apr. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.18 (1961:Apr. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    By New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. no.19 (1961:Apr. 25). Item is in English.